Inventory of the Nell Eurich papers 1922-2000
Hoover Institution Archives
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Research files for The Learning Industry
    - Target groups
      - Professionals
        - Occupations
          - Physicians
            - Other literature
              - Southern Medical Association, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 46: 4)
      - Missing persons
        - General, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 46: 5)
        - Articles, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 46: 6)
        - Research studies, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 46: 7)
        - Other literature
          - General, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 46: 8)
          - Hudson Institute, Workforce 2000, 1987 (Box-folder 46: 9)
        - General Education Development Test (GED), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 46: 10)
        - Handicapped, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 47: 1)
        - Immigration and cultural diversity, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 47: 2)
        - Poverty and two-tiered society, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 47: 3)
        - Literacy
          - Statistics, 1986 (Box-folder 47: 4)
          - Articles, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 47: 5)
          - Research studies
            - Literacy report by Julie Wilson, 1988, undated (Box-folder 47: 6)
            - Southport Institute for Policy Analysis final report, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 47: 7)
            - Woodrow Wilson Task Force literacy research
              - General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 47: 8)
              - Report and authors B through K, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 48: 1)
              - Authors L through T, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 48: 2)
          - Other literature
            - American Society for Training and Development (ASTD) literacy project, 1987 (Box-folder 48: 3)
            - Pennsylvania State University (Penn State) Institute for the Study of Adult Literacy, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 48: 4)
          - Technology
            - Approaches, 1988 (Box-folder 49: 1)
            - Hightech workplace, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 49: 2)
            - Using TV and Computer Assisted Instruction (CAI), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 49: 3)
            - Pennsylvania State University (Penn State) Adult Literacy and Technology Conference, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 49: 4)
            - Support by MacArthur Foundation, 1988 (Box-folder 49: 5)
  - Corporations
    - Programs
      - Managers and professionals
        - General, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 49: 6)
        - Articles, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 49: 7)
        - Research studies, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 49: 8)
        - Programs for managers and accountants
          - Arthur Andersen & Co., 1987-1988 (Box-folder 49: 9)
          - Bell South, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 49: 10)
          - KPMG Peat Marwick, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 49: 11)
          - Other programs, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 49: 12)
        - Programs for engineers
          - AT&T Bell Labs, Academy for Computer Science and Engineering, 1986 (Box-folder 50: 1)
          - Boeing, 1986 (Box-folder 50: 2)
          - Burroughs, after hours program, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 50: 3)
          - Hewlett-Packard
            - Staff-oriented interviews, 1986, undated (Box-folder 50: 4)
            - Topic-oriented interviews, 1986 (Box-folder 50: 5)
            - Other materials, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 50: 6)
          - Honeywell Technical Education Program, 1986, undated (Box-folder 50: 7)
          - Hughes Aircraft Company, 1988 (Box-folder 50: 8)
          - International Business Machines (IBM), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 50: 9)
          - Texas Instruments, 1986 (Box-folder 50: 10)
      - Missing persons
        - Correspondence and memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 50: 11)
        - Articles, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 50: 12)
        - Research studies, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 51: 1)
        - ABC/PBS, Project Literacy U.S. (PLUS), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 51: 2)
        - Business Council for Effective Literacy (BCEL), 1984-1988 (Box-folder 51: 3)
        - Control Data, PLATO delivery system, undated (Box-folder 51: 4)
        - Gannett Foundation, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 51: 5)
        - International Business Machines (IBM)
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 51: 6)
          - Other literature, 1986, undated (Box-folder 51: 7)
          - Principle of the Alphabet Literacy System (PALS) videotape and manual, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 52: 1)
            Includes one VHS tape
    - Distance education and delivery systems
      - Articles, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 52: 2)
      - AT&T, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 52: 3)
      - Digital Equipment Corporation, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 52: 4)
      - International Business Machines (IBM), circa 1988 (Box-folder 52: 5)
  - Vendors
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 52: 6)
    - Articles, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 52: 7)
    - Other literature
      - General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 52: 8)
      - National Education Corporation, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 52: 9)
  - Education
    - Programs
      - Professionals
        - Programs for engineers, 1983-1988, undated (Box-folder 52: 10)
        - Purdue University, construction engineering, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 52: 11)
    - Distance education and delivery systems
      - Organizations and networks
        - Association of College and University Telecommunication Administrators, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 53: 1)
        - International University Consortium, 1987, undated (Box-folder 53: 2)
        - National Science Foundation Supercomputer Network, 1987 (Box-folder 53: 3)
        - National University Teleconference Network (NUTN), 1987 (Box-folder 53: 4)
        - Other organizations and networks, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 53: 5)
      - Schools
        - American Open University, New York Institute of Technology, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 53: 6)
        - Buena Vista College, Iowa, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 53: 7)
        - California State University, 1988 (Box-folder 53: 8)
        - California State University, Chico, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 53: 9)
        - Colorado State University, videotape short courses, 1986 (Box-folder 53: 10)
        - Columbia Video Network, New York, 1986-1987, undated (Box-folder 53: 11)
        - Kansas State University, 1987 (Box-folder 53: 12)
        - New School, New York, Connect.Ed, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 53: 13)
        - Nova University, Florida, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 53: 14)
        - Oklahoma State University, 1988, undated (Box-folder 53: 15)
        - Oklahoma Network of Continuing Higher Education, 1986 (Box-folder 53: 16)
        - Rochester Institute of Technology, New York, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 53: 17)
        - Saybrook Institute, California, 1988 (Box-folder 53: 18)
        - University of Arizona, 1988, undated (Box-folder 54: 1)
        - University of Maryland, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 54: 2)
        - University of Southern California, Instructional TV Network, 1986 (Box-folder 54: 3)
        - University of South Carolina, Engineering School, 1987 (Box-folder 54: 4)
        - University of South Florida, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 54: 5)
        - University of Wisconsin, 1986, undated (Box-folder 54: 6)
        - Virginia Cooperative Graduate Engineering Program, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 54: 7)
        - Other schools, 1981-1986, undated (Box-folder 54: 8)
    - Community colleges
      - General, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 54: 9)
      - Articles, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 54: 10)
      - Cohen-Brawer study
        Commissioned research: Arthur Cohen and Florence Brawer
        - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 54: 11-12)
        - Staff commentaries, 1987 (Box-folder 54: 13)
        - Report and background information, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 54: 14)
      - American Association of Community and Junior Colleges
        - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 55: 1)
        - Other literature, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 55: 2)
      - Community College IBM Information Sharing System (CCIISS) Database, 1988 (Box-folder 55: 3)
      - Research studies
        - Educational Testing Services, 1987 (Box-folder 55: 4)
        - Fred Pincus, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 55: 5)
        - Lee Teitel, 1987 (Box-folder 55: 6)
      - Schools
        - Alpena Community College, Michigan, 1986 (Box-folder 55: 7)
        - Anne Arundel Community College, Maryland, 1986 (Box-folder 55: 8)
        - Borough of Manhattan Community College, New York, 1988 (Box-folder 55: 9)
        - Bristol Community College, Massachusetts, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 55: 10)
- Education, training, and technology file
  - Adult learning and higher education
    - Bank Street College Education, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 56: 1)
    - Bok, Derek, "Toward Education of Quality,", 1986 (Box-folder 56: 2)
    - Bugliarello, George, Polytechnic Institute of New York, 1988 (Box-folder 56: 3)
    - Continuing Education Units (CEU), 1986 (Box-folder 56: 4)
    - Dill, William, correspondence and articles, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 56: 5)
    - Forrester, Jay, articles, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 56: 6)
    - Harvard University Medical School, 1984 (Box-folder 56: 7)
    - Higher education current issues, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 56: 8)
    - Kerr, Clark, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 56: 9)
    - Lynton, Ernest A., 1981-1983, undated (Box-folder 56: 10)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT)
      - Center for Arts and Media Technology, notes, undated (Box-folder 56: 11)
      - Lifelong learning for electrical engineers, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 56: 12)
    - New York University graduate School of Business Administration, 1983 (Box-folder 56: 13)
    - Northwestern University, 1988 (Box-folder 56: 14)
    - Pew Memorial Trust
      - General, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 56: 15)
      - Liberal Arts Enrichment Program, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 56: 16)
    - Public Broadcasting Service, "The New American Campus,", 1987 (Box-folder 56: 17)
    - Rockefeller College, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 56: 18)
    - State University of New York, Rockefeller Institute of Government, Jane Zacek, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 57: 1)
    - University of California, Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 57: 2)
    - University of Massachusetts, Boston, Gerontology Institute, 1992 (Box-folder 57: 3)
    - University of Pennsylvania, Wharton School, 1982 (Box-folder 57: 4)
    - University of Virginia, Miller Center, undated (Box-folder 57: 5)
    - University research centers, conference material for International Conference on University Affiliated Research Parks, 1986 (Box-folder 57: 6)
    - University Seminar Center (USC), undated (Box-folder 57: 7)
    - Urban Whitaker, Center for Innovative Programs and The Learning Center, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 57: 8)
      Includes "Profiles in Adult Learning," a TV series for which Eurich interviewed
  - Secondary education
    - Benedum Foundation, 1988 (Box-folder 57: 9)
    - Doyle, Denis, American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, 1984 (Box-folder 57: 10)
    - Kolderie, Ted, Center for Policy Studies, "Public Services Redesign Project,", 1990 (Box-folder 57: 11)
    - Know, Amie B., 1988-1989 (Box-folder 57: 12)
      See also Woodrow Wilson Foundation
    - Low, Frances, 1987 (Box-folder 57: 13)
    - Paideia Bulletin, Institute for Philosophical Research, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 57: 14)
    - Recruiting young teachers, 1988, undated (Box-folder 57: 15)
    - School reform, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 57: 16)
    - Wetzel, James R., "American Youth: A Statistical Snapshot,", 1989 (Box-folder 57: 17)
  - Private and nonprofit organizations
    - Center for Community Economic Development, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 57: 18)
    - Education Commission of the States (ECS) Business Advisory Commission, papers on state education policies, 1986 (Box-folder 57: 19)
    - Gross, Ronald, correspondence and articles, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 57: 20)
    - Information Industry Association, Robert Vitro, 1988 (Box-folder 58: 1)
    - National Center for Development of Education, Leslie Koltai, 1987 (Box-folder 58: 2)
    - National Center for Education and the Economy, 1988 (Box-folder 58: 3)
    - National Institute for Work and Learning, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 58: 4)
    - Pew Partnership for Civic Change, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 58: 5)
    - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 58: 6)
  - Government agencies
    - General Accounting Office (United States), 1986 (Box-folder 58: 7)
    - Maryland State Board of Higher Education, "State Initiatives to Promote Technological Innovation and Economic Growth,", 1986 (Box-folder 58: 8)
    - National Institute of Education (USDOE), Pennsylvania study, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 58: 9)
    - Office of Education Research and Improvement (OERI-USDOE), "Transforming American Education: Reducing the Risk to the Nation,", 1986 (Box-folder 58: 10)
    - Office of Technology Assessment (OTA/US Congress), "Technology and the American Economic Transition,", 1988 (Box-folder 58: 11)
  - Business and industry
    - Association of Management Consulting Firms, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 58: 12)
    - Brown, Gordon, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 58: 13)
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Federal Government
    - Branch programs
      - Department of Labor
        - Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA)
          - Other literature
            - Book excerpts and legislation items, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 59: 1)
            - Directories, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 59: 2)
            - National Alliance of Business, "Is the Job Training Partnership Working?", 1986 (Box-folder 59: 3)
            - National Commission for Employment Policy, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 59: 4)
            - Westat, 1985 (Box-folder 59: 5)
    - Distance education and delivery systems, 1988 (Box-folder 59: 6)
  - Military
    - Memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 59: 7)
    - Articles, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 59: 8)
    - Research studies
      - P. D. Jenkins report "Training in the Military,", 1987 (Box-folder 60: 1-2)
      - Military Manpower training reports, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 60: 3)
      - National Center for Research in Vocational Education, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 60: 4)
        Includes memorandum
    - Other literature
      - Defense Activity for Non-Traditional Education Support (DANTES), 1986-1987, undated (Box-folder 60: 5)
      - Military Career Guide, undated (Box-folder 60: 6)
    - Schools
      - National Defense University, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 61: 1)
      - Air Force, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 61: 2)
      - Navy, 1986 (Box-folder 61: 3)
      - Army, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 61: 4)
    - Programs
      - Technical workers, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 61: 5)
      - Managers
        - General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 61: 6)
        - Articles, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 61: 7)
        - Other literature, schools and courses, 1987, undated (Box-folder 61: 8)
      - Professionals, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 61: 9)
        Includes materials concerning Naval Postgraduate School
      - Missing persons
        - General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 61: 10)
        - Basic Skills Education Program (BSEP) and Job Skills Education Program (JSEP), 1986-1989 (Box-folder 61: 11)
        - Research studies, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 61: 12)
    - Distance education and delivery systems
      - Memoranda and research studies, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 61: 13)
      - Air Force Extension Course Institute, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 61: 14)
  - Nonprofit organizations
    - Programs
      - Missing persons
        - 70001 Training & Employment Institute, 1986 (Box-folder 62: 1)
        - American Library Association (ALA)
          - General, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 62: 2)
          - Research studies, 1981-1988, undated (Box-folder 62: 3)
          - Queens Borough Public Library, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 62: 4)
        - Comprehensive Competency Program (CCP)/Taggart/U. S. Basics Skills Investment Corporation, 1988 (Box-folder 62: 5)
        - Laubach Literacy Action, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 62: 6)
        - Literacy Volunteers of America, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 62: 7)
        - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation, 1988 (Box-folder 62: 8)
        - Opportunities Industrialization Centers of America, 1987-1988, undated (Box-folder 62: 9)
    - Research organizations
      - Think tanks, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 62: 10)
      - Abt Associates, Inc., 1987 (Box-folder 62: 11)
      - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 62: 12)
      - Brookings Institute, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 63: 1)
      - Carnegie Forum on Education and the Economy, 1987 (Box-folder 63: 2)
      - Cato Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 63: 3)
      - Centers of Excellence Project, Carnegie Corporation, 1985 (Box-folder 63: 4)
        Report by James Botkin and Dan Dimancescu
      - Citizens for a Sound Economy, 1986 (Box-folder 63: 5)
      - Conference Board, 1987 (Box-folder 63: 6)
      - ERIC National Center for Research in Vocational Education, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 63: 7)
      - Ford Foundation, 1987 (Box-folder 63: 8)
      - Heritage Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 63: 9)
      - Hoover Institution, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 63: 10)
      - Hubert H. Humphrey Institute, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 63: 11)
      - Hudson Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 63: 12)
      - National Center for Educational Brokering, 1986 (Box-folder 63: 13)
      - National Institute for Work and Learning, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 63: 14)
      - Public Agenda Foundation, undated (Box-folder 63: 15)
      - Research Institute for Higher Education, Hiroshima University, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 63: 16)
      - Rand Corporation, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 64: 1-2)
      - Syracuse University, Kellogg Project, 1988 (Box-folder 64: 3)
      - University and technology research, 1987 (Box-folder 64: 4)
      - Urban Institute, 1986 (Box-folder 64: 5)
      - W. E. Upjohn Institute for Employment Research, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 64: 6)
      - Work in America Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 64: 7)
  - Conferences
    - 1988 (Box-folder 64: 8)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 64: 9)
    - Training and personnel conference, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 64: 10)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 64: 11)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 64: 12)
- Education, training, and technology file
  - Education
    - Clippings, articles, and papers, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 65: 1)
    - Perelman, Lewis J., Strategic Performance Services, "The Real Crisis in Education and Training: A Challenge for the Governors,", 1985 (Box-folder 65: 2)
    - Slater, Joseph, World City/Phoenix resort/cruise project, 1987 (Box-folder 65: 3)
    - Springer-Verlag Publishing Company, 1985 (Box-folder 65: 4)
  - Adult education and higher learning
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Drafts and notes for The Learning Industry
    - Other manuscript material and notes
      - Staff assignments, 1987 (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - Materials pursuant to publication
    - Author's summary, undated (Box-folder 66: 2)
    - Clippings and publicity, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 66: 3)
    - Press releases, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 4)
    - Mailing lists, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 66: 5)
  - Post-publication materials
    - Statistics on the workforce, 1990 (Box-folder 66: 6)
    - Correspondence
      - Beall, Donald R., Chairman of the Board and CEO of Rockwell International Corporation, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 7)
      - Craig, Robert L., 1991 (Box-folder 66: 8)
      - Dickinson, Dee, author of New Horizons for Learning, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 9)
      - Eberle, W. D., 1991 (Box-folder 66: 10)
      - Ellet, William C., 1991 (Box-folder 66: 11)
      - Fretwell, E. K., Jr., 1989-1991 (Box-folder 66: 12)
      - Gross, Ronald, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 13)
      - Hewitt, Colby, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 14)
      - Koerner, Thomas F., National Association of Secondary School Principals, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 15)
      - Mitra, C. R., New Delhi National Institute of Information Technology, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 16)
      - Settle, Theodore J., 1991 (Box-folder 66: 17)
      - Walker, Samuel R. and Allmon, Joseph, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 18)
      - General correspondence and memoranda
        - In reply to books sent by Nell Eurich, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 19)
        - In reply to books sent by Maurice Lazarus, 1991 (Box-folder 66: 20)
        - Boyer, Ernest L., 1990-1991 (Box-folder 66: 21)
        - Correspondence with Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching (CFAT), 1990 (Box-folder 66: 22)
        - Kellogg Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 66: 23)
        - General, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 67: 1)
        - Memoranda, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67: 2)
    - Other literature
      - American Society for Training & Development (ASTD), 1989 (Box-folder 67: 3)
      - Business-Higher Education Forum, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 67: 4)
      - Carnegie Commission on Science, Technology, and Government, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67: 5)
      - Public Agenda Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67: 6)
      - Southport Institute for Policy Analysis, Alan Pifer, Forrest Chisman, 1991 (Box-folder 67: 7)
    - Background issues
      - Competitiveness, 1990 (Box-folder 67: 8)
      - Future predictions, 1989 (Box-folder 67: 9)
      - Workforce, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67: 10)
    - Target groups
      - Trade and technical workers, 1984, undated (Box-folder 67: 11)
      - Managers
        - Bibliography, 1989 (Box-folder 67: 12)
        - International School of Information Management, Eric Boehm, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 67: 13)
      - Professionals, continuing education, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67: 14)
      - Missing persons
        - Literacy and basic education, 1989 (Box-folder 67: 15)
        - Minority issues, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67: 16)
    - Technology and training
      - Delivery technology
        - General, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67: 17)
        - Information networks, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67: 18)
        - Literacy, 1987 (Box-folder 67: 19)
      - Artificial intelligence, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67: 20)
      - Learning theory, 1990 (Box-folder 67: 21)
    - Education
      - American Association of Community and Junior Colleges (AACJC), 1991 (Box-folder 67: 22)
      - Continuing education, 1991 (Box-folder 67: 23)
      - Proprietary schools, 1990, undated (Box-folder 67: 24)
    - Federal government
      - Department of Education, America 2000: An Education Strategy, 1991 (Box-folder 67: 25)
      - Department of Labor, Center for Advanced Learning Systems (CALS), 1991 (Box-folder 68: 1)
      - Legislation, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 68: 2)
      - Office of Technology Assessment, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 68: 3)
      - Office of Technology Assessment, Linda Roberts, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 68: 4)
    - Military
      - General, 1991 (Box-folder 68: 5)
      - Articles and other literature, 1990, undated (Box-folder 68: 6)
      - John E. Buckley, Chicago Seminar, 1990-1991, undated (Box-folder 68: 7)
    - Corporations
      - Articles, 1991 (Box-folder 68: 8)
      - Corporate annual reports, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 68: 9)
- Education, training, and technology file
  - Partnerships
    - Business partnerships (K-12), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 68: 10)
    - Center for Public Resources, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 68: 11)
    - College Board Office of Adult Learning Services, 1986 (Box-folder 68: 12)
    - Cooperative programs, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 68: 13)
    - Corporate Council on the Liberal Arts
      - General, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 69: 1)
      - Symposium, 1986 (Box-folder 69: 2)
    - Council for Adult and Experimental Learning, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 69: 3)
    - Cross, Patricia, "Partnership with Business and the Professions,", 1981-1983 (Box-folder 69: 4)
    - Educational Facilities Laboratories (EFL), 1976-1985 (Box-folder 69: 5)
    - Keck, Mary Jane, proposed analysis of corporation and secondary school needs, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 69: 6)
    - Liberal arts and business, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 69: 7)
    - Manhattenville College, adult and corporate classes, 1986 (Box-folder 69: 8)
    - McKinney, Claude A., North Carolina State University and Research Triangle Park, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 69: 9)
    - McQuigg, Beverly, "Role of Education in Industry,", 1980 (Box-folder 69: 10)